<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on CW</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on CW</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:52:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>nocebo effect</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/nocebo_effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:52:45 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/nocebo_effect/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nocebo: said to occur when a patient&amp;rsquo;s negative expectations for a treatment cause the treatment to have a worse effect that it otherwise would&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Placebo: said to occur when positive expectations improve an outcome&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both effects are psychogenic, meaning they originate from the mind but they can produce measurable physical effects on the body. While a placebo effect improves a condition, nocebo can produce a wide range of symptoms such as nausea, stomach pains, itching, bloating, depression, and sleep problems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cozy bear</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/cozy_bear/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:50:11 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/cozy_bear/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s blog post is about Cozy Bear, which sounds really cute, but is actually is a Russian hacker group that is believed to be acting on behalf of Russia&amp;rsquo;s foreign intelligence service (SVR). They are known by many names such as Cozykar, CozkRuke, Office Monkeys, and APT29.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;APT standing for advanced persistent threat, which describes threats that may lay undetected for a long time before acting and are often motivated politically or economically. &amp;ldquo;Dwell time&amp;rdquo; is the official term for how long these groups go undetected, with a median time in the Americas of 71 days.&#xA;APT groups usually follow a similar lifecycle:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Words1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/words1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 21:42:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/words1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a page about »Words1«.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>quantum entanglement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/quantum_entanglement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 01:17:27 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/quantum_entanglement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quantum entanglement is a concept I came across in the TikTok comments of a post about how a couple met. According to some, falling in love and being in a relationship is similar to the mechanics of quantum entanglement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quantum entanglement is &amp;ldquo;a complex phenomenon that is usually poorly described as an invisible link between distant quantum objects that allows one to instantly affect the other &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/quantum-entanglement-isnt-all-that-spooky-after-all1/&#34;&gt;Ferrie&lt;/a&gt;. Einstein once described it as &amp;ldquo;spooky action at a distance&amp;rdquo; and was not a huge fan of quantum physics which was alledgedly solidified by a famous paper he helped write that claimed quantum physics was incomplete.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ephemera</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/ephemera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 15:32:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/ephemera/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Definition: items of collectible memorabilia, typically written or printed ones, that were originally expected to have only short-term usefulness or popularity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, vintage items that were maybe one-time use or not expected to be collectible later. Great examples of ephemera include postage stamps, newspapers, stickers, cigarette boxes, snack wrappers. They serve as a great visual reference to specific time periods and can be used as obscure inspiration for graphic design, marketings, etc.s&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lava lamps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/first_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lava lamps is such a random name for a blog right?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps they are the most random thing possible. This is precisely why Cloudflare, an internet security company, uses them to generate encryption keys.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because computers can never really generate random numbers, you must look to the real world instead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The lava blobs in lava lamps never take the same shape twice and move in inconsistent ways, not really following a pattern, similar to the way a candle flickers or a leaf blows in the wind. Cloudflare uses a series of cameras pointed at the lamps to generate data points (numbers) for starting points for their encryption keys.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
